Finding aid for Library (University of Michigan) Clipping file, ca. 1920-1980
Bentley Historical Library
- University of Michigan
  - L
    - Law School-Keniston (Hayword) Lectures on Liberal Education and Democratic Institutions. 1956-.
    - Law School-Law Quadrangle. (Box 35)
      (Includes: Lawyers Club, John P. Cook Dorm, Legal Research Library, Hutchins Hall, etc. Materials on buildings and dedication. see also: Law School-Lawyers Club; Law School-Library.)
    - Law School-Lawyers Club. (Box 35)
      (see also: Law School-Lawyers Club-Founder's Day)
    - Law School-Lawyers Club-Founder's Day. (Box 35)
    - Law School-Legal Aid Clinic.
      (see: Societies-Law School.)
    - Law School-Legal Research. (Box 35)
      (see also: Law School-Library; Law School-Publications; Law School-Law Quadrangle (for Legal Research Bldg.))
    - Law School-Legal Research Library.
      (see: Law School-Library.)
    - Law School-Library (Box 35)
    - Law School-Practice Court.
      (Held in Civil Procedures 3 course. Reenacts accident cases jointly with other units, i.e. Medical School, Mich. State Police, etc. see Law School.)
    - Law School-Publications. (Box 35)
      (see also: Law School-Legal Research)
    - Lawler Committee.
      (see: Student Records)
    - Lawyers Liberal Club.
      (see: Societies-Law School)
    - Le Cercle Francais.
      (see: Societies-Le Cercle Francais League Banquet and Installation; Women's League.)
    - League Building.
      (Includes Board of Governors, library, Barbara Little Music Room and phonorecord concerts, cafeteria, Grand Rapids Room, ballroom. Built by the Alumnae Council. see also: League Building-Social Activities; Alumnae Council.)
      - 1920-1924 (Box 36)
      - 1925-1926 (Box 36)
      - 1927-1928 (Box 36)
      - 1929 (Box 36)
      - 1930-1946 (Box 36)
      - 1947- (Box 36)
    - League Building-Lydia Mendelssohn Theater. (Box 36)
      (Includes physical description, some movies and plays (1929-34). For productions given here see various organizations: e.g. Play Production; Dramatics-Dramatic Festival; Dramatics, etc.)
    - League Building-Social Activities.
      (Includes general use of facilities for bridge and dance classes, League Fair, Open House, joint League-Union activities. For events sponsored by the Women's League, see also: 'Women's League-Activities. For Theater see also: League Bldg.-Lydia Mendelssohn Theater.)
      - 1929-1939 (Box 36)
      - 1940-1954 (Box 36)
      - 1955- (Box 36)
    - League Council.
      (see: Women's League.)
    - League for Industrial Democracy.
      (see: Political Clubs-Round Table Club.)
    - League for Liberal Action.
      (see: Political Clubs-Socialist. League Houses. see: Housing-Women.)
    - League of Nations. Study groups-
      (see: Political Clubs-International Relations; Discussions-see: Campus Events, 1932-1934)
    - League of Women Voters.
      (see: Political Clubs-Non-partisan groups.)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on.
      (see: Center for Research on Learning and Teaching.)
    - Lecture and Poetry Series. (Box 36)
    - Lecture Bureau.
      (see: Extension.)
    - Lecture Committee.
      (see: Free Speech.)
    - Lecture Series.
      (see: Oratorical Series.)
    - Lecture Series (SS).
    - Lectures, speeches, etc.
      (see: Lectures sponsored by a specific group are under the name of the group. e.g.: Oratorical Series; .Journalism, Dept. of-Lectures; Law School-Cook Lectures; For lectures sponsored by no one group or the university as a whole see: Campus Events; Summer Session-Campus Events. Lectures, speeches, etc. Continued; For questions on selection of speakers see: Free Speech; Radicals; Student Government. Also U-M PhD thesis-Kinney, Stanley-The Selection of Outside Speakers by Student Organizations at U-M (1854-1935). 1956 (No. 4396).)
    - Legal Aid Clinic.
    - Legal Aid Service for Students (1967-).
      (see: Student Government (Sponsored by Student Govt. Council).)
    - Legal Aspects of Atomic Energy. A joint Phoenix Project and Law School program.
      (see: Phoenix Project-Research.)
    - Legal Research Archives.
    - Legal Research Center 1950-.
      (Set up for research on written law; service to organization and faculty; and publication of materials. see: Law School-Legal Research.)
    - Legal Research Institute. Sponsored by the Lawyers Club Foundation
      (see: Law School-Legal Research.)
    - Legislative Advisory Council on Problems of the Aging. a Michigan state society.
      (see: Institute for Human Adjustment-Gerontology, Division of.)
    - Legislative Research Center 1949-.
    - (Muriel.) Lester House.
      (see: (card) Intercooperative Council, Inc. (folder.) Cooperative rooming and boarding projects.)
    - Letter to Michigan Alumni.
      (see: Alumni Publications. Liberal Discussion Group. see: Political Clubs.)
    - Liberal Students Union.
      (see: Religion-Churches-Unitarian.)
    - Library.
      (see also: cards following and Business Administration, School of (for Bus. Ad. Lib.); Clements (W.L.) Lib.; Dearborn Campus; History-Michigan Historical Collections; Kresge Medical Library; Law School-.Library; Transportation Inst. and Lib.)
      - 1920-1928 (Box 36)
      - 1929-1935 (Box 36)
      - 1936-1939 (Box 36)
      - 1940-1946 (Box 36)
      - 1946-1953 (Box 36)
      - 1954 (Box 36)
    - Library-Exhibits.
      - 1915-1929 (Box 36)
      - 1930-1947 (Box 36)
      - 1948- (Box 36)
    - Library-Extension (Box 36)
    - Library-Gifts and Special Collections.
      (see also: Library-Labadie Collection. Library-Stellfield Collection; Library-Manuscripts and Papyri; Transportation Institute and Library; Kresge Medical Library; Clements Library; History-Michigan Historical Collections; Law School-Library.)
      - 1909-1929 (Box 36)
      - 1930-1949 (Box 36)
      - 1950- (Box 36)
    - Library-Labadie Collection. (Box 36)
    - Library-Manuscripts and Papyri. (Box 36)
    - Library-Quarto.
      (see: Clements Library-Quarto.)
    - Library-Staff. (Box 36)
      (see also: Faculty-Bishop, W.W.; Faculty-Rice, Warner; Faculty-Wagman, Fredrick)
    - Library Staff Association. Library Notes. (Box 36)
    - Library-Stellfield Collection. (Box 36)
      (see also: Faculty-Cre-Cu (Louise Cuyler))
    - Library-Undergraduate (Box 36)
    - Library Leaflet.
      (see: Library-Publications.)
    - Library Science, Dept. of, clippings (Box 36)
    - Life Guard Corps.
    - Life magazine, International ed. March 22 issue with article on U. of M. see Student Life, 1965
    - Linguistic Institute. For earlier work in linguistics
      (see: Speech, Dept. of Sponsored by MiU and the Linguistic Society of America)
      - 1936-1944 (Box 36)
      - 1945-1956 (Box 36)
      - 1957 (Box 36)
    - Linguistic Society of America
      (see: Linguistic Institute)
    - Linguistics, classical.
      (See: Classical Studies, Dept. of)
    - Linguistics, foreign language; see the foreign language group concerned i.e., Germanic Lang. and Lit. Romance Lang. and Lit. Far Eastern Lang. and Lit.
    - Linguistics Club.
    - Liquor Problem.
    - Literary College.
      (Includes Literary College Conferences. see also: Faculty evaluations; Curriculum; Student-FacultyAdministration Relations (for SFA Conferences); Literary College-Residential Coll.)
      - 1946-1956 (Box 36)
      - 1957-1965 (Box 36)
      - 1966-1969 (Box 36)
    - 1969-1972 (Box 37)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 37)
    - Literary College-Residential College. (Box 37)
    - Little, President Clarence Cook
      - Clippings
        - 1926 (Box 37)
        - 1927-1929 (Box 37)
          (Resignation)
        - 1929- (Box 37)
      - Bibliography (Box 37)
      - Inauguration (Box 37)
      - Speeches, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Little Club.
      (see: Association for Independent Men.)
    - "Little Club" 1966-.
      (see: University Activities Center.)
    - Little Symphony.
      (see: Orchestras)
    - Little Theater of Willow Village.
      (see: Dramatics-Student Players)
    - (Alice Crocker) Lloyd Radiation Therapy Center and Lloyd Memorial Isotope Research Laboratory.
    - Loan Collections.
      (see: Art Print Loan Collection; Extension-Audio-Visual Education Center. (Art Masterwork Collection))
    - Loan Funds-clippings (Box 37)
      (see also: Scholarships; Fellowships; Finances-Trust Funds.)
    - Lord Chamberlain's Players.
    - Lost and Found.
      (see: Administration October 1968; Student Activities Center.)
    - (Henry Martin) Loud Foundation Lectures.
    - Dr. P.C. Lowery Award.
    - Lunar Science Institute (Houston, Texas)
    - Lutheran Student Center and Chapel.
      (see: Religion-Churches Lutheran.)
    - Lydia Mendelssohn Theater.
      (see: League Building-Lydia Mendelssohn Theater.)
  - M
    - "M" Club.
      (see: Athletics-Societies)
    - MacArthur for Emperor.
      (see: Political Clubs-Democrats Mace. see: Symbols)
    - McInally (Wm. K.) Lecture.
      (see: Business-Administration, School of McNaught Awards in Journalism. see: Journalism, Dept. of)
    - Macromolecular Research Center.
    - Madelon Pound House. Addition to the International Center.
    - Mailing Service.
      (see: Service Enterprises)
    - Maintenance.
    - Maison Francaise.
      (see: Romance Languages and Literature, Dept. of)
    - Mammalian Genetics Center. (Box 37)
    - Management Information System (MIS).
    - Management of Personnel Quarterly (v.1, no.1, November 1961-)
    - Managers Club.
    - Manuscripts and Papyri.
      (see: Library-Manuscripts and Papyri)
    - Marine Reserves.
      (see: Naval Science, Dept. of)
    - Marital Education. (Box 37)
    - Marketing Club.
      (See: see: Societies-BA)
    - Marketing System. (grading) (Box 37)
      (see also: Literary College (Conferences); Calendar (Schedules); Graduate School (Graduate Record Exam.) Student Records (Class ranking of students))
    - Markley House.
      (see: Cooperative Rooming and Boarding Projects.)
    - Marriage and Family Life Series.
      (see: Extension-Detroit.)
    - Masons.
    - Masques.
      (see: Dramatics-Masques.)
    - Mathematics, Dept. of (Box 37)
      (Includes Math. Clubs, Insurance. see also: Computers; Statistics, Dept)
    - Matrix Table dinner. see; Theta Sigma Phi
    - May Day Incident (1934).
      (see: Radicals-May Day Incident.)
    - May Festival.
    - Mayalan Language.
      (see: Far Eastern Studies.)
    - Mechanical Engineer's Club.
      (see: Societies-Engineering.)
    - Medical Center, 1958-.
      - 1958-1967 (Box 37)
      - 1968- (Box 37)
    - Medical Center-Clinical Research Unit.
      (see: Medical School-Research.)
    - Medical Center Alumni Society Conference.
      (see: Societies-Medical School.)
    - Medical Library.
      (see: Kresge Medical Library.)
    - Medical School.
      (Includes faculty, courses, lectures, clinics', building program for Medical School. see also: Hospitals; Medical School-Research; Medical School Merger; Simpson Memorial Institute for Medical Research; Societies-Galens; Societies-Medical School.--plus related schools, e.g.-Dentistry; Nurses; Pharmacy; Public Health; Expansion (3rd medical school?))
      - 1911-1929 (Box 37)
      - 1930-1936 (Box 37)
      - 1936-1939 (Box 37)
      - 1940-1944 (Box 37)
      - 1945-1949 (Box 37)
      - 1950-1953 (Box 37)
    - 1954-1957 (Box 38)
    - 1957-1964 (Box 38)
    - 1965-1969 (Box 38)
    - 1970-1974 (Box 38)
    - 1974- (Box 38)
    - Medical School -- Post Graduate Medicine (Box 38)
    - Medical School-Research.
      (Includes Kresge Medical Research Bldg. Before 1930 see: Medical School. see also: Kresge Med. Lib.; Simpson Inst. for Med. Research; Hospitals; Mental Retardation Research)
      - 1930-1956 (Box 38)
      - 1957-1965 (Box 38)
      - 1966- (Box 38)
    - Medical School-Societies.
    - Medical School merger (1922).
    - Medical Science Building.
      (see: Medical School.)
    - Medical Technologist Society.
    - Medieval Festival.
      (see: Dramatics-Student Groups.)
    - Medieval Society.
      (see: History, Dept. of)
    - Memorials. (Box 38)
      (see also: names of individuals (e. g. Faculty-Cooley, Thos. M. for Milles Fountain).)
    - (Ann Arbor) Mennonite Fellowship.'
    - Men's Education. Club/and/ Men and Women's Education Club.
      (see: Societies-Education.)
    - Men's Glee Club.
      (See: Glee Clubs.)
    - Men's Judiciary Council.
      (see: 1939-47-Student Affairs Committee; 1947-51-Joint Judiciary Council. Replaced 1952 by Joint Jud. Council.)
    - Men's Student Council., 1935-1939
      (see: Student Government.)
    - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 38)
      (Formerly a branch of the Neuropsychiatric Institute under the name Mental Health Research Unit). see also: Psychiatry.)
    - Mental Retardation Research. An interdisciplinary center. (Box 38)
    - Arthur H. Merritt Award.
    - Mesopotamian Archaeological Expedition. (to Parthian Sites at Seleucia).
      (see: Near Eastern Studies-Mesopotamia Expedition Kelsey Museum of Archaeology; Faculty-Waterman.)
    - "Messiah". (Choral Union Christmas program presentation).
    - Metamorphosis. Campus produced movie, 1951.
      (see: Moving Pictures-Gothic Film Society.)
    - Meteorology and Oceanography. (Box 38)
      (Includes Meteorological Lab.)
    - Metropolitan Club. (Students from NYC and NJ).
      (see: Societies-G-P.)
    - Mexican Symposium, 1958.
      (see: Latin-American Relations.)
    - Mexico. El Oliver School. A joint project.
      (see: Vocational Education and Practical Arts, Dept. of.)
    - Michifish.
      (see: Swimming and Aquatic Sports-Women.)
    - Michigamua.
      (see: Societies-Michigamua)
    - "Michigan".
      (see: Summer Session-Campus Events (1955).)
    - Michigan Academy of Science, Arts, and Letters.
      (see: Michigan Academy of Science, Arts, and Letters. (general file).)
    - Michigan Actuarial Club.
      (see: Societies-Business Administration.)
    - Michigan Alumnus. For clippings
      (see: Alumni-Publications.)
    - Michigan Alumnus Quarterly Review. (Box 38)
    - Michigan Christian Fellowship.
      (see: Religion-Michigan Christian Fellowship)
    - Michigan Citizenship Clearing House (Student Chapter)
      (see: Political Clubs)
    - Michigan Committee for Academic Freedom.
      (see: Political Clubs-Michigan Youth for Democratic Action.)
    - Michigan Council of Teachers of English.
      (see: English Language and Literature, Dept. of-Conferences.)
    - Michigan Council on Economic Education.
    - Michigan Crib.
      (see: Societies-Michigan Crib.)
    - Michigan Daily.
      (Originally "Chronicle". Includes Michigan Weekly. see also: Student Publications (for general info.); Students, Outstanding)
    - 1920-1929 (Box 38)
    - 1930-1938 (Box 38)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 38)
    - 1941-1944 (Box 38)
    - 1945-1952 (Box 38)
    - 1953-1958 (Box 38)
    - 1958- (Box 38)
    - Michigan Dames.
      (see: Societies-Michigan Dames.)
    - "Michigan Day"
      (see: Union.)
    - Michigan Economic Development Commission.
      (Includes a:number of faculty members). see Planning Boards-Michigan (general file))
    - Michigan Executive Study Group.
      (Composed of business executives and U-M faculty. Published four studies on plant location thru the School of Business Administration). see: Michigan-Industries (general file))
    - Michigan Forensic Forum.
      (see: Michigan Forum.)
    - Michigan Forester. Forestry annual.
      (see: Natural Resources, School of 1950-)
    - Michigan Forum. (Box 38)
      (Sponsored by Student Legislature and now Student Government Council. Also called Michigan Forensic Forum. Includes America's Town Meeting of the Air. see also: Political Clubs.)
    - Michigan High School Forensic Association.
      (see: Bureau of School Services (sponsor).)
    - Michigan Historical Collections.
      (see: History-Michigan Historical Collections.)
    - Michigan (Socialist) House.
      (see: (card)-Intercooperative Council, Inc.; (folder)-Cooperative rooming and boarding projects.)
    - Michigan House Plan.
      (see: Housing.)
    - Michigan Interscholastic Press Association
      (see: Journalism, Dept. of.)
    - Michigan Interuniversity Committee on Information Systems (MICIS)
      (see: Computers.)
    - Michigan Journalist.
      (see: Journalism, Dept. of-Michigan Journalist)
    - Michigan League.
    - Michigan Metallurgical Society.
      (see: Societies-Engineering. Michigan)
    - Music Festival.
      (see: Music, School of-Extension Program "Michigan Nights" (Early Radio broadcasting). see: Radio.)
    - Michigan Orchestral Festival.
      (see: Orchestras.)
    - Michigan Party. One of the parties created by the Student Senate.
      (see: Student Senate.)
    - Michigan Schoolmasters Club.
      (see: Michigan Schoolmasters Club (general file).)
    - Michigan Singers. Small extra-curricular choral group (counterpart vocally of the Chamber Orchestra).
      (see: Glee Clubs-Extra-curricular groups.)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows. (Box 38)
    - Michigan Technic.
      (see: Engineering, College of-Technic.)
    - Michigan. Weekly.
      (see: Michigan Daily.)
    - Michigan Wolverine Restaurant.
    - Michigan Youth for Democratic Action (MYDA).
    - Michigan Youth Symphony.
      (see: Music, School of-Extension Program.)
    - Michiganensian.
      - 1920-1942 (Box 38)
      - 1943- (Box 38)
    - Michigania, Camp. (Alumni Family Camp, Walloon Lake).
      (see: Alumni Association.)
    - Michigras. 1905-
      (Sponsored by 'Union and W.A.A. Called Union Fair 1905-24, Michigras 1937-9, Michilodeon 1941-6, Michigra 1947-Winter Weekend, 1965. (including Sesquigras, 1967).)
      - 1937-1951 (Box 38)
      - 1952-1958 (Box 38)
      - 1958- (Box 38)
    - Michilodeon.
      (see: Michigras.)
    - Microbiology.
      (see: Bacteriology, Dept. of.)
    - Microfilms.
      (see: Photoreproduction Services.)
    - Middle English Dictionary.
      (see: English Lang. and Lit., Dept. of)
    - Midwest Community College. Leadership Program.
      (see: Education, School of-Higher Education.)
    - Midwest Institute on Public Relations for the Bar.
      (Sponsored jointly by the State Bar of Michigan and the U. of M. Law School. 1953-see: Law School-Institutes.)
    - Midwestern Music Conference.
      (see: Music, School of-)
    - Midwestern Conference on School Vocal and Instrumental Music.
    - Military Affairs, Office of. (Box 39)
      (Admin. off. giving info. on selective service). see also: WW2-Military and Naval Service; Marking System (for class ranking of Male students); For military units on campus, see: R.O.T.C.; Air Science, Dept. of; Naval Science, Dept. of;(includes Marines); Societies, Military; WW2-Army and Navy Educ. Program.;)
    - Military Ball.
      (see: Societies-Military.)
    - Military Research (Classified research under contract).
    - Military Science and Tactics, Dept. of.
      (see: R.O.T.C.)
    - Miller (Norman F.) Gynecologic Society.
    - Milles (Carl) Fountain.
      (see: Faculty-Cooley, Thomas M (A Memorial))
    - Ed. C. and Nellie White Mills Prize Essay Award.
    - Mimes.
      (see: Union-Opera-Mimes. Mimes Theater. see: Union-Theater)
    - Mineral Collection (Natural Science Bldg.)
    - Mineralogy, Dept. of. For Geology-Mineralogy Journal Club (Box 39)
      (see: Societies-Science.)
    - Modern Jazz Society.
      (see: Jazz.)
    - Modern Language Association.
    - Modern Poetry Club.
      (see: Societies-Literary.)
    - Modern Views of Man and Society.
      (see: Summer Session-Campus Events. (1952))
    - Monte Carlo Ball. Sponsored by the International Students Association
      (see: Foreign Students-International Students Association.)
    - Monteith, John.
      (see: Presidents.)
    - Monuments.
      (see: Memorials.)
    - George R. Moore Award.
    - Moratorium.
      (see: Activism; Ann Arbor-Politics and Govt. (for A. A. activity Viet Nam (for US Activity))
    - Mormons (Latter Day Saints).
    - Morris Hall (Formerly home of radio broadcasting at MiU)
      (see: Radio.)
    - Mortar Board.
      (see: Societies-Mortar Board)
    - Motion picture library.
      (see: Extension. Audio-visual Education Center.)
    - Motorcycles, Scooters.
      (see: Bicycles, Motorcycles.)
    - (Charles S.) Mott Foundation.
      (see: Gift to Flint College see: Flint Branch; Lectures in religion see: Religion.)
    - Moving Pictures
      (Includes of M. made movies, general and misc. films. Films sponsored by a particular group will he found under that group. see also: Moving Pictures-Art Cinema League;-Cinema Guild,-Gothic Film Society; League-Lydia Mendelssohn Theater (for some early films); Societies-Hillel (for Hillel Film Society); Extension-Audio-Visual Education Center)
      - 1927-1962 (Box 39)
      - 1962-1975 (Box 39)
    - Moving Pictures-Art Cinema League (1932-50).
      (Replaced by Student Legislature's Cinema Guild 1950.)
      - 1932-1940
      - 1941-November 1948
      - December 1948-1950
    - Moving Pictures-Cinema Guild.
      (Superseded Art Cinema League in 1950. see also: Censorship (for Flaming Creatures case or similar incidents))
      - 1950-1953 (Box 39)
      - 1953-1956 (Box 39)
      - 1957-1970 (Box 39)
      - 1971-1974 (Box 39)
    - Moving Pictures-Gothic Film Society 1949- (Box 39)
    - Mu Phi Epsilon.
      (see: Societies-Mu Phi Epsilon.)
    - Mud Bowl.
      (see: Alumni-Homecoming.)
    - Municipal Purchasing Conference.
      (see: Institute of Public Administration.)
    - Municipal training.
      (see: Bureau of Government.)
    - Museum of Anthropology.
      (see: Anthropology, Dept. of;)
    - Museums
    - Museum of Art.
      - 1920-1945 (Box 39)
      - 1946-1949 (Box 39)
      - 1950-April 1957 (Box 39)
      - 1958-1963 (Box 39)
      - 1964-1968 (Box 39)
      - 1969-1973 (Box 39)
    - Museum of Art and Archaeology.
      (see: Kelsey Museum of Archaeology.)
    - "Museum of Fine Arts".
      (These are really exhibits in Rackham. (see: Graduate School-Exhibits in Building. see also: Fine Arts, Dept. of)
    - Museum of Natural History. old title
      (see: Museums.)
    - Museum of Paleontology.
      (Includes the Hall of Evolution. see: Museums)
    - Museum of Zoology.
      (see: Museums. Annual reports includes Museums (pamphlets))
    - Museums. University Museums
      (consists of Museum of Anthropology; Museum of Zoology; Museum of Paleontology; Herbarium; Krieger Mycological Library; Hall of Evolution;. Hall of Biological Principles;)
      - 1921-1930 (Box 39)
      - 1930-1937 (Box 39)
      - 1938-1959 (Box 39)
      - 1953-1957 (Box 39)
      - 1958 (Box 39)
    - Museums--Other museums on campus
      (see: Museum of Art; Kelsey Mus. of Archaeology; Dept. of Mineralogy (Collections);)
    - Music.
      (Includes only misc. items and data on Michigan songs. see also: cards for: Bands; Burton Tower; Choirs; Chamber Music; Glee Clubs; Gilbert and S. Society; Hill Auditorium; Jazz; Music, School of; Music Series; Opera; Organ; Orchestras Societies-Music; Interlochen Music Camp. Collegium Musicum (Renaissance and Baroque Music) Power Center for the Performing Arts.)
      - 1920-1955 (Box 39)
      - 1956- (Box 39)
    - Music, School of
      (Includes: .general data on the faculty and curriculum, student and faculty recitals (for School of Music chamber groups, see: Chamber Music, music library, student council (Music School Assembly), Composer's Forums (1950-), and composition program. see also: Music, School of Extension Program; Music, School of-Midwestern Conference; Bands; Burton Tower; Chamber Music; Glee Clubs; Collegium Mus.; Music Series; Organ; Orchestra; Opera; Societies-Music;)
      - 1921-1933 (Box 40)
      - 1934-1940 (Box 40)
      - 1941-1947 (Box 40)
      - 1948-1952 (Box 40)